How was the exam, Lily?
考试考得怎样  俐俐
Not too bad. I think I passed in English and Mathematics.
不算太坏  我想我的英语和数学及格了
The questions were very easy.
题目很容易
How about you, Mia?
你怎么样  米亚
The English and Maths papers weren't very easy for me.
英语和数学试题对我来说不很容易
I hope I haven't failed.
我希望别不及格
I think I failed the French paper.
我想我的法语及不了格
I could answer sixteen of the questions.
我能回答其中的16道题
They were very easy.
这些题很容易
But I couldn't answer the rest.
但我回答不出剩下的题
They were too difficult for me.
那些题对我来说太难了
French tests are awful, aren't they?
法语太可怕了  你说呢
I hate them.
我讨厌法语
I'm sure I've got a low mark.
我的法语分数肯定很低
Oh, cheer up!Perhaps we didn't do too badly.
啊  别灰心  或许我们考得还不太糟
The guy next to me wrote his name on top of the paper.
坐在我旁边的那个人只在试卷顶端写自己的名字
-Yes? -Then he sat there and looked at it for three hours!
-然后呢  -然后他就坐在那里  对着考卷看了3个小时
He didn't write a word!
他一个字也没写